Łukasz Gonciarz

https://pl.linkedin.com/in/łukasz-gonciarz-9b351398

https://github.com/vanluke https://www.npmjs.com/~goncarz email: gonciarz.lukasz@enginner.com

mobile: 795 637 279

location: Cracow



About me

Passionate in Software

Experienced Senior Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry.

My area of interest is Software Architecture.

Strong engineering professional with a Master of Science (MSc)

Frontend developer

Javascript evangelist, architect.

I am a passionate and self-motivated. I love to share my knowledge and discuss all the software aspect.

I am always up to date.

As a developer I am experienced in all aspects of designing and developing web based projects.

Bringing ideas to life

Skills & Abilities

JAVASCRIPT

- ES2015/ES2016/ES2017 /ES2018
- JSON, AJAX
- Libraries: Lodash, Underscore, jQuery, sinon, highcharts, morris, c3, alt.js, redux, firebase, redux-observables, rxjs
- Frameworks: ReactJS, AngularJS, Angular2, Aurelia.io, Knockout
- Test frameworks (mocha, karma, protractor, jest)

CSS3, HTML5

- CSS frameworks: Bootstrap, Material Design,
- Saas (Scss)

NOSQL DATABASES

Experience with MongoDB, Firebase, Couch DB,

NODEJS

- Express
- Koa
- Koa2

SQL	
Oracle PL/SQLMicrosoft SQL Server TSQL · MySQL,SQLite	
VERSION CONTROL	TOOLS
• GIT • TFS	 Dev Tools Editors / IDE: Atom, Sublime Text, Visual Studio, VS Code, Task runner: automation tools: Gulp, Grunt, npm scripts Project/Task management: TFS, Jira, Trello, Webpack

Education

MASTER OF SCIENCE | 2015-06-27 | CRACOW UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY | COMPUTER SCIENCE

- Degree 5.0
- Graduated with distinction

ENGINEERING DEGREE | 2014-02-10 | CRACOW UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY | COMPUTER SCIENCE

- Degree 5.0
- Graduated with distinction
- Related coursework: KNI Scientific Circle Cracow University of Technology Computer Science, 1st place at the University Session of the Scientific Circles

Experience

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER | CODETE GmbH | 2016-12-14

- · Bringing ideas to frontend word
- Frontend Team Lead
- Projects: Gelato Optimalprint Repurchase Dashboard, University4Industry

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER | FIRST-UTLITY | 2016-11-01 - 2016-12-14

- Performing audit
- Helps moving forward. Provides best practises and solution for frontend
- Projects: Maxcare

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER | INTIVE (SMT SOFTWARE SERVICES) | 2016-08-01 - 2016-10-31

- Technical verifications
- Project estimations
- Buildings web applications with various technologies

Projects: Tandem Bank

CONSULTANT (FRONTEND)| INFUSION DEVELOPMENT POLAND | 2015-07-01 - 2016-07-31

- Mainly focusing on web application. Roles included: software engineer, front end web developer, back-end developer. Designing and developing new and improving existing applications
- Projects: Budget Dashboard, Infusion Procurement Portal. Employee Management Portal

ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT | INFUSION DEVELOPMENT POLAND | 2014-08-01 - 2015-06-30

- Working with a client mainly focusing on web application. Designing and developing new applications
- Projects: ADP Expertise Locator, Shale Inland Sales Connect, Muppetshow

.NET DEVELOPER | FQS POLAND | 2014-01-01 - 2014-07-31

- Designing and developing application based on big data (xbrl)
- Projects: XBRL

NET DEVELOPER | COMARCH | 2013-07-01 - 2013-12-31

- Developing web applications
- Projects: Comarch e-pracownik, Comarch Asysta

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE DEVELOOPER | ASSECO POLAND | 2012-08-01 - 2013-02-01

- Working mainly with big data.
- Designing, analyzing and developing databases, aggregating and analyzing data coming from various data sources

Certificates

- MCSD: Web Applications
- OCA Oracle Database 11g Administration 1Z0-052
- Introduction to Oracle9i: SQL 1Z0-007

Projects

University4Industry

- Senior Frontend Developer
- Technology stack: ReactJS, redux, Materia-ui, sass(scss), jest, webpack, nock, html5

Gelato Optimalprint Repurchase Dashboard

· Frontend team lead

 Technology stack: ReactJS, redux, sass(scss), react-bootstrap, webpack, mocha, jsdom, chai, nock, html5, PHP

MAXCARE

- Responsibility: code review. Give idea how to improve and maintain big scale application
- Technology stack: ReactJS, graphql, mocha, express, html5

TANDEM BANK

- Bank application
- · Responsibility: Frontend
- Technology stack: Javascript, Sass(Scss), HTML5, Angular, Typescript, karma, ASP .NET WebApi, webpack

EMPLOYEE MANAGEMENT PORTAL

- Application that manage Employee in companies
- I was responsible for frontend
- Technology stack: ReactJS, Javascript, ASP .NET WebApi, HTML5, Sass (Scss), MS SQL Server, webpack

BUDGET DASHBOARD

- Application for managers. Application aggregates all spend, budgets and deliver to a user in a smart, elegant way. It includes powerful charts (d3) to provide better understanding of expenses in the company
- I was responsible entirely for a forntend
- Technology stack: Javascript, Aurelia.io, ASP .NET Web Api, F#, Saas, HTML5, MS SQL Server

INFUSION PROCUREMENT PORTAL

- Application that handles all procurement request in company. It also include all some visualization to give understanding of procurements in the company
- My responsibility was to create entire application
- Technology stack: ASP .NET WebApi, Javascript, AngularJS, TypeScript MS SQL Server, CSS3, html5, gulp

ADP - EXPERTISE LOCATOR

- Search engine that gives ability to deliver detailed information about People connected with employer. Responsibility: front-end and back-end (NodeJS)
- Technology stack: JavaScript, AngularJS, NodeJS (with express), HTML5, SASS

SHALE INLAND - SALES CONNECT

- Project for Shale Inland web application that allows sales operators work with the clients everywhere, in any time.
- · Responsibility: frontend and backend
- Technology stack: Javascript (Type script), AngularJS, SaaS, CSS3, html5, ASP .NET WebAPI, HTML5, MS SQL Server, NHibernate, Azure

MUPPETSHOW

- Application that aggregate entire public information about employer
- · Responsibility: frontend and backend
- Technology stack: Javascript, AngularJS, ASP .NET MVC, ASP .NET WebAPI, CSS3, HTML5, grunt

COMARCH E-PRACOWNIK

- Comarch ERP e-Pracownik is an application to manage working time with the module Payroll and HR Optima ERP Comarch Comarch ERP ERP XL and Comarch Altum.
- Technology stack: Javascript, Typescript, ASP .NET MVC, WCF, HTML5, CSS, MS SQL Server

COMARCH ASYSTA

- Web application for reporting notifications (bugtracker)
- Technology stack: ASP .NET Web Forms, Javascript, CSS, HTML5, WCF, MS SQL Server

Hobbies

- · Cycling amateur, enthusiast,
- · Cooking in my free time I like baking cakes,
- Skiing amateur, enthusiast,
- Automotive interesting in old fashioned and modern cars, IT, new technologies. I want always more

Languages

- Polish
- English

Others

· Driving license

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2002, item 1182 as amended.